{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957512905","data":{"timestamp":" 946957512905"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957520771","data":{"timestamp":" 946957520771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957544114","data":{"timestamp":" 946957544114"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957579104","data":{"timestamp":" 946957579104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 53137f04-3dea-496c-a836-a077300f4db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957588059","data":{"timestamp":" 946957588059"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957591428","data":{"timestamp":" 946957591428"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957596479","data":{"timestamp":" 946957596479"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957598625","data":{"timestamp":" 946957598625"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957605899","data":{"timestamp":" 946957605899"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957610039","data":{"timestamp":" 946957610038"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957610911","data":{"timestamp":" 946957610911"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957612113","data":{"timestamp":" 946957612113"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957612314","data":{"timestamp":" 946957612313"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 77dc9230-9941-4cd8-b348-5254cb514889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957621461","data":{"timestamp":" 946957621461"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 306a7da9-3d70-4958-9ea8-adcfdb56bfb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957621685","data":{"timestamp":" 946957621685"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 306a7da9-3d70-4958-9ea8-adcfdb56bfb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957622648","data":{"timestamp":" 946957622648"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 306a7da9-3d70-4958-9ea8-adcfdb56bfb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957623692","data":{"timestamp":" 946957623692"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 306a7da9-3d70-4958-9ea8-adcfdb56bfb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957623859","data":{"timestamp":" 946957623859"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 306a7da9-3d70-4958-9ea8-adcfdb56bfb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957636714","data":{"timestamp":" 946957636714"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957641578","data":{"timestamp":" 946957641578"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957645253","data":{"timestamp":" 946957645253"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957648623","data":{"timestamp":" 946957648622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957648812","data":{"timestamp":" 946957648812"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:10..910.off100.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957663098","data":{"timestamp":" 946957663097"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957676648","data":{"timestamp":" 946957676648"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 6734d74e-f974-4ee2-8a22-4fbe065a4cec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957686096","data":{"timestamp":" 946957686096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" c95da8dc-4d3e-4ade-8b54-e0c823a42c33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957686322","data":{"timestamp":" 946957686321"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" c95da8dc-4d3e-4ade-8b54-e0c823a42c33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957687288","data":{"timestamp":" 946957687288"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" c95da8dc-4d3e-4ade-8b54-e0c823a42c33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957688561","data":{"timestamp":" 946957688561"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" c95da8dc-4d3e-4ade-8b54-e0c823a42c33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957689512","data":{"timestamp":" 946957689512"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" c95da8dc-4d3e-4ade-8b54-e0c823a42c33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957689596","data":{"timestamp":" 946957689596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" c95da8dc-4d3e-4ade-8b54-e0c823a42c33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957705729","data":{"timestamp":" 946957705729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" afca3dc9-3fea-479a-848c-aff5ac25ca4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957705771","data":{"timestamp":" 946957705770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" afca3dc9-3fea-479a-848c-aff5ac25ca4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957705935","data":{"timestamp":" 946957705935"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" afca3dc9-3fea-479a-848c-aff5ac25ca4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957738730","data":{"timestamp":" 946957738730"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_427_283-427-149"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 427"," userResponse":" 427"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957750315","data":{"timestamp":" 946957750315"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_717_528-717-494"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 717"," userResponse":" 717"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957763483","data":{"timestamp":" 946957763483"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_132_132-863-423"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 132"," userResponse":" 132"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957780118","data":{"timestamp":" 946957780118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_193_193-178-308"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 193"," userResponse":" 308"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957831902","data":{"timestamp":" 946957831902"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_193_193-178-308"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 193"," userResponse":" 193"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957844109","data":{"timestamp":" 946957844109"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_713_152-713-495"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 713"," userResponse":" 713"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957855430","data":{"timestamp":" 946957855430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_166_848-298-166"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 166"," userResponse":" 166"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957879706","data":{"timestamp":" 946957879706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_246_385-246-463"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 246"," userResponse":" 246"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957891144","data":{"timestamp":" 946957891143"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_624_624-574-310"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 624"," userResponse":" 624"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957903642","data":{"timestamp":" 946957903641"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_235_353-235-171"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 235"," userResponse":" 235"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957917737","data":{"timestamp":" 946957917737"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_789_602-557-789"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 789"," userResponse":" 789"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957927866","data":{"timestamp":" 946957927866"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_789_602-557-789"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957933552","data":{"timestamp":" 946957933552"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_789_602-557-789"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957951101","data":{"timestamp":" 946957951101"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_789_602-557-789"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957963926","data":{"timestamp":" 946957963926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" 329a1712-ed17-499f-955d-c30d6abdf7c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL1.incr.76"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_789_602-557-789"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958150038","data":{"timestamp":" 946958150037"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" fa4fff3d-c535-4ff0-96c8-671060218cfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_667_569-667-477"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 667"," userResponse":" 667"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958170360","data":{"timestamp":" 946958170359"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_064440"," gameId":" fa4fff3d-c535-4ff0-96c8-671060218cfe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF5-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_461_449-714-461"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 461"," userResponse":" 449"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}